Some stories end with a beginning.
Wander Darkly is a romance, drama film directed by Tara Miele.
New parents Adrienne and Matteo are forced to reckon with
trauma amidst their troubled relationship.
They must revisit the memories of their past and unravel haunting
truths in order to face their uncertain future.
Adrienne, played by Sienna Miller.
Matteo, played by Diego Luna.
Patty, played by Beth Grant.
Steve, played by Brett Rice.
Maggie, played by Vanessa Bayer.
Shea, played by Aimee Carrero.
Wander Darkly is a 2020 American drama film written and directed by Tara Miele.
The film stars Sienna Miller, Diego Luna, Beth Grant, Aimee
Carrero, Tory Kittles, and Vanessa Bayer.
Wander Darkly had its world premiere at the Sundance Film Festival on January 25, 2020,
and was released in the United States on December 11, 2020, by Lionsgate.
The tone is emotional.